{
    "id": "3c7bd42efbc5495fa3ebec367c2748ac",
    "title": "Irregular Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I .......................... the bell twice but no one opened the door.",
            "description": "Rang is the past tense of ring.",
            "answers": [
                "ring",
                "rang",
                "rung"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ............................ your violin?",
            "description": "Brought is the past tense of bring.",
            "answers": [
                "bring",
                "bringed",
                "brought"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Your cat has ........................... all the milk.",
            "description": "Drunk is the past participle form of drink. We use the past participle after drink.",
            "answers": [
                "drink",
                "drank",
                "drunk"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She ................................ the clothes dry.",
            "description": "Wrung is the past tense of wring.",
            "answers": [
                "wring",
                "wrung",
                "wringed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They ............................... a deep well.",
            "description": "Dug is the past tense of dig.",
            "answers": [
                "dig",
                "dug",
                "digged"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ............................... the whole day in bed.",
            "description": "Spent is the past tense of spend.",
            "answers": [
                "spend",
                "spent",
                "spended"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The place ............................. of damp.",
            "description": "The past tense of smell can be smelled or smelt. ",
            "answers": [
                "smelled",
                "smelt",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She ................................ like a star at the party.",
            "description": "Shone is the past tense of shine.",
            "answers": [
                "shine",
                "shined",
                "shone"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I .............................. some juice on the carpet.",
            "description": "The past tense of spill is spilled or spilt.",
            "answers": [
                "spilled",
                "spilt",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly a brilliant idea ................................. me.",
            "description": "Struck is the past tense of strike.",
            "answers": [
                "strike",
                "struck",
                "struk"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was wearing a ................................ shirt.",
            "description": "Torn is the past tense of tear.",
            "answers": [
                "torn",
                "tored",
                "tore"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I .............................. up hearing a noise.",
            "description": "Woke is the past tense of wake.",
            "answers": [
                "waked",
                "woke",
                "woked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}